Tufts Hillel Records UA244
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Tufts Hillel Records
1979 -- 2018
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Tufts Hillel
Summitt, Jeffrey
UA244
4.45 Linear Feet
53 Gigabytes
197 Digital Object(s) 197 digital objects comprising 5825 files.
This collection contains the records of Tufts Hillel, including physical and digital event and program documentation, publications, and files created or collected by Rabbi Summit, former Jewish Chaplain and Director of Tufts Hillel.
Conditions Governing Access
This series contains some restricted material. Restrictions related to specific material are listed in the detailed contents list. This series may require review before it is available for use. Please contact DCA for further details.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Transferred by Tufts Hillel, 2018.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged in three series: 2018 accessions; Born digital materials; and Rabbi Summit papers.
Biographical / Historical
Tufts Hillel was founded during World War II with the goal of promoting Jewish life and culture at Tufts. It was founded by and remains affiliated with Hillel International, which works to promote Jewish life on college campuses.
Tufts Hillel is a student-run organization that sponsors social, cultural, educational, and religious programs and events that reach the entire Tufts community. These activities have included lecture series, Yiddish and Hebrew language classes, Shabbat services, and a Holocaust and genocide studies program. Tufts Hillel also runs a full range of religious services and meals for all Jewish holidays and has partnered with Tufts Dining to provide kosher dining options on campus.
In 1994, Tufts Hillel built and opened the Granoff Family Hillel Center at 220 Packard Avenue, which provides offices, meeting spaces, and kosher kitchens and still serves as the home of Tufts Hillel.
Rabbi Jeffrey Summitt was the Executive Director of Tufts Hillel from 1979-2018. Rabbi Naftali Brawer was appointed Tufts' Jewish Chaplain and Neubauer Executive Director of Tufts Hillel in May 2018.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains event and program flyers, physical photographs of Hillel events and programs, publications, media, and digital photographs and video recordings of events sponsored or attended by Tufts Hillel. This collection also contains subject and office files created or collected by Rabbi Summit during the course of his work as Jewish Chaplain and Director of Tufts Hillel, including administrative material, information on Judaic Studies courses, program reports and grant records, correspondence, and material related to the Granoff Family Hillel Center and its Ark.
Biographical / Historical
Jeffrey A. Summit (1950 - ) served as Jewish Chaplain and Neubauer Executive Director of Tufts Hillel from 1979-2018. He became Jewish Chaplain Emeritus in July 2018. Summit has served as a Research Professor in the Department of Music and Judaic Studies at Tufts since 2012.
Jeffrey A. Summit graduated from Brandeis University in 1972. He received his rabbinic ordination and an M.A.H.L. from Hebrew Union College-Jewish Institute of Religion in 1975. He holds an M.A. (1988) and Ph.D. (1995) at Tufts University in Ethnomusicology through the Interdisciplinary Doctoral.
Summit came to Tufts in 1979 as the Jewish Chaplain and Neubauer Executive Director of Tufts Hillel, a position he held until 2018. Under his direction, the Hillel program at Tufts was nationally recognized for its focus and active engagement on issues such as social justice and active citizenship, interfaith and intercultural cooperation, and Israeli-Palestinian conflicts. He received the inaugural Edgar M. Bronfman Award for Lifetime Accomplishment in Hillel Professional Leadership from Hillel International in 2014. In 2018, he received the Hosea Ballou Medal at Tufts for his leadership and service at Tufts Hillel. As of 2018, Summit continues to serve as a Senior Consultant at Hillel International, directing the program "Living Our Values."
Summit also played an important role at the Tufts European Center in Talloires, France, where he taught and led summer programs, and has been a research professor in the Department of Music and Judaic Studies at Tufts since 2012.
Summit is the author of two books: Singing God's Words: The Performance of Biblical Chant in Contemporary Judaism (2016), and The Lord's Song in a Strange Land: Music and Identity in Contemporary Jewish Worship (2000). In 2001, Summit founded the Abayudaya College Scholarship Project, which works with the Jewish Abayudaya community in Uganda and raises and administers funds to send students from the community to colleges and universities. Collaborating with photojournalist Richard Sobol, Summit co-authored Abayudaya: The Jews of Uganda, published in 2002. He also recorded, compiled, and annotated the music album Abayudaya: Music from the Jewish People of Uganda for Smithsonian Folkways Recordings, released in 2003. The album was nominated for a GRAMMY Award for best album in the category of Traditional World Music. In 2003, his album Delicious Peace: Coffee, Music and Interfaith Harmony in Uganda, also for the Smithsonian Folkways Recordings, won "best traditional world music CD" at the Independent Music Awards.
Student life; Judaism; Granoff Family Hillel Center; Student Affairs and Services; Student life; Student activism; Alumni and Alumni Relations; Foreign affairs
- 2018 accessions, circa 1983 -- 2017; UA244.001; 2.4 Linear Feet
  Conditions Governing Access
  This series is open for research.
  Arrangement
  This material is arranged in received order.
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains event and program flyers, photographs of Hillel events and programs, publications, and media.
  - Israel Festival Photos, 2008; UA244.001.001.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1)
    Open for research.
  - India Summer Trip Photobook, 2010 -- 2010; UA244.001.001.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1)
  - Agahozo Shalom Youth Village Trip Photobook, 2009 -- 2010; UA244.001.001.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1)
  - Argentina Summer Trip Photobook, 2011; UA244.001.001.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1)
  - Academic Year Program Reports, 2000 -- 2003; UA244.001.001.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1)
  - Programming: High Holidays, 2002 -- 2015; UA244.001.001.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1)
  - Pathways Conference, 2007 -- 2008; UA244.001.001.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1)
  - Programming: Jewish Learning, 1983 -- 1998; UA244.001.001.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1)
  - Capital Campaigns: Granoff Family Hillel Center, circa 1994 -- 2005; UA244.001.001.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1)
  - Programming Calendars, 1996 -- 2001; UA244.001.001.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1)
  - Programming Calendars, 2002 -- 2006; UA244.001.001.00011; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1)
  - Programming Calendars, 2007 -- 2009; UA244.001.001.00012; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1)
  - Programming Calendars, 2009 -- 2016; UA244.001.001.00013; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1)
  - Alumni Programming, 2002 -- 2007; UA244.001.001.00014; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1)
  - Development: "From the Center" newsletter, 1996 -- 2006; UA244.001.001.00015; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1)
  - Development: "From the Center" newsletter, 2007 -- 2017; UA244.001.001.00016; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1)
  - Vitality: Health and Wellness Programming, circa 2000 -- 2013; UA244.001.001.00017; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1)
  - Merrin Moral Voices Programming, 2012 -- 2016; UA244.001.001.00018; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1)
  - Chai Week Programming, 1998 -- 2000; UA244.001.001.00019; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1)
  - Passover Programming, 2000 -- 2011; UA244.001.001.00020; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1)
  - Holocaust and Genocide Education, 1999 -- 2015; UA244.001.001.00021; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1)
  - Israel Programming, circa 2015; UA244.001.001.00022; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1)
  - "Koleinu" Magazine, circa 2000 -- 2002; UA244.001.001.00023; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1)
  - Programming: 2006-2007, UA244.001.001.00024; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1)
  - Programming: 2007-2008, UA244.001.001.00025; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1)
  - Programming: September 08-February 09, 2008 -- 2009; UA244.001.001.00026; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1)
  - Programming: March-December 2009, UA244.001.001.00027; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1)
  - Programming: January 2010-2014, UA244.001.001.00028; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1)
  - Programming: 2013-2014, UA244.001.001.00029; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1)
  - Programming: 2014-2015, UA244.001.002.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2)
  - Photographs, 1989 -- 1992; UA244.001.002.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2)
  - Slides and negatives, circa 1990 -- 2010; UA244.001.002.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2)
  - Negatives and oversize photographs, circa 1990 -- 2010; UA244.001.002.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2)
  - Tzedek/Education; Religious and Social Events photographs, circa 2000 -- 2004; UA244.001.002.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2)
  - Birthright/Israel; misc. photographs, circa 2000 -- 2008; UA244.001.002.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2)
  - Morgan Spurlock Moral Voices Lecture VHS, 2013; UA244.001.002.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2)
  - Alan Keyes Lecture VHS, 2002; UA244.001.002.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2)
  - "Truth to Power" Lecture VHS, 2001; UA244.001.002.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2)
  - Israel Celebrates 60 DVD, 2007; UA244.001.002.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2)
- Born digital materials, circa 2002 -- 2017; UA244.002; 197 Digital Object(s) 197 digital objects comprising 5825 files.; 53 Gigabytes; .25 Linear Feet
  This series is open for research, but may require review before it is available for use. Records on digital media have been stabilized and made available via Box. Note that files were not converted for access and all may not be viewable in Box. Please contact DCA for further details.
  This series is arranged alphabetically and by format. File titles were provided by Tufts Hillel.
  This series contains photographs and video recordings of events sponsored or attended by Tufts Hillel.
  - CDs and DVDs, circa 1990 -- 2017; UA244.002.003; .25 Linear Feet (Box 25, 122, 3, 7, 36)
    Immediate Source of Acquisition
    Transferred by Tufts Hillel, 2018, accession UA-2018-035.
    This file is open for research, but is minimally processed and may require review before it is available for use. Please contact DCA for further details.
    This file contains photographs and video and audio recordings of events sponsored or attended by Tufts Hillel.
  - 1-22-09 Israel lecture, 2009; UA244.002.00001; 5 Digital Object(s); 13.7 Megabytes
  - 12-4-13 Hanukkah Party, 2013; UA244.002.00002; 55 Digital Object(s); 115.9 Megabytes
  - 2009 Adele's Kitchen Best jpg, UA244.002.00003; 17 Digital Object(s); 50.6 Megabytes
  - 3-05-09 Concert, 2009; UA244.002.00004; 18 Digital Object(s); 49 Megabytes
  - 8-31-08-Bagel-Brunch, 2008; UA244.002.00005; 112 Digital Object(s); 343.7 Megabytes
  - 9-17-08 Read by the River GI, 2008; UA244.002.00006; 9 Digital Object(s); 18.3 Megabytes
  - 9-22-08 Bagel Brunch upperclassmen, 2008; UA244.002.00007; 37 Digital Object(s); 89.6 Megabytes
  - 9-7-08-BBQ, 2008; UA244.002.00008; 45 Digital Object(s); 139 Megabytes
  - 9-8-08-General-Interest, 2008; UA244.002.00009; 34 Digital Object(s); 92 Megabytes
  - Alt_Spr_Brk_Tampa, circa circa 2002 -- 2017; UA244.002.00010; 4 Digital Object(s); 0.22 Megabytes
  - Alt_Spr_Brk_Tampa_09_Max_Orenstein, 2009; UA244.002.00011; 60 Digital Object(s); 0.52 Megabytes
  - Alumni - Miracle Martini Nights - 01-10-09 and 01-08-09, 2009; UA244.002.00012; 6 Digital Object(s); 1.9 Megabytes
  - Alumni Bagel Brunch 2014, UA244.002.00013; 38 Digital Object(s); 199.6 Megabytes
  - Alumni Cooking with Adele Bacow - Spring 2011, UA244.002.00014; 17 Digital Object(s); 26.3 Megabytes
  - Alumni Dodgeball 2014, UA244.002.00015; 3 Digital Object(s); 0.36 Megabytes
  - Alumni Miracle Martini Nights - Jan 2009, UA244.002.00016; 161 Digital Object(s); 311.3 Megabytes
  - Alumni Neighborhood Shabbat Dinners 2015, UA244.002.00017; 5 Digital Object(s); 8.7 Megabytes
  - Alumni Passover Cooking Event, circa circa 2002 -- 2017; UA244.002.00018; 28 Digital Object(s); 49.8 Megabytes
  - Ambassador Dennis Ross Lecture, circa circa 2002 -- 2017; UA244.002.00019; 52 Digital Object(s); 593.8 Megabytes
  - Apple Picking 2013, UA244.002.00020; 9 Digital Object(s); 1.4 Megabytes
  - Ari Shavit Lecture- 1.21.2016, 2013; UA244.002.00021; 107 Digital Object(s); 168.1 Megabytes
  - Art Green Lecture 2014, UA244.002.00022; 23 Digital Object(s); 91.9 Megabytes
  - A_BagelBrunchUpperclass, circa circa 2002 -- 2017; UA244.002.00023; 4 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes
  - Bagel Brunch 2014, UA244.002.00024; 90 Digital Object(s); 515 Megabytes
  - Baltics Alternative Spring Break 2014, UA244.002.00025; 370 Digital Object(s); 885.9 Megabytes
  - Benefit Show - March7-2002, UA244.002.00026; 18 Digital Object(s); 5.4 Megabytes
  - Birthright GIM 2014, UA244.002.00027; 14 Digital Object(s); 10.4 Megabytes
  - Birthright Summer 2015, UA244.002.00028; 204 Digital Object(s); 543.9 Megabytes
  - Birthright Trips, circa circa 2002 -- 2017; UA244.002.00029; 12 Digital Object(s); 15.8 Megabytes
  - Board of Directors Meeting 10.18.09, 2009; UA244.002.00030; 1129 Digital Object(s); 305.2 Megabytes
  - BOD Meeting February 2014, UA244.002.00031; 12 Digital Object(s); 35.1 Megabytes
  - Bowel Bash, 4-8-05, 2005; UA244.002.00032; 16 Digital Object(s); 5.1 Megabytes
  - Building, circa circa 2002 -- 2017; UA244.002.00033; 2 Digital Object(s); 2.8 Megabytes
  - B_Israel, circa circa 2002 -- 2017; UA244.002.00034; 25 Digital Object(s); 14.9 Megabytes
  - Chanukah 2013, UA244.002.00035; 60 Digital Object(s); 126.2 Megabytes
  - Chanukkah Casino Night 12.10, 2010; UA244.002.00036; 15 Digital Object(s); 42.5 Megabytes
  - Climate Change and Gender Based Violence, circa circa 2002 -- 2017; UA244.002.00037; 21 Digital Object(s); 75.3 Megabytes
  - Cummings Keynote 2014 Eva Kor, UA244.002.00038; 75 Digital Object(s); 309 Megabytes
  - Cummings Keynote 2015 Rena Finder, UA244.002.00039; 40 Digital Object(s); 469.1 Megabytes
  - C_Bacow Cooking, circa circa 2002 -- 2017; UA244.002.00040; 6 Digital Object(s); 17.7 Megabytes
  - Donna Mitchell Lecture 2014, UA244.002.00041; 10 Digital Object(s); 169.7 Megabytes
  - D_Bat mitzvah, circa circa 2002 -- 2017; UA244.002.00042; 5 Digital Object(s); 12.7 Megabytes
  - Erin Brock Lecture Photos, circa circa 2008 -- 2012; UA244.002.00043; 14 Digital Object(s); 77.8 Megabytes
  - E_aKZTrip, circa circa 2002 -- 2017; UA244.002.00044; 11 Digital Object(s); 28.2 Megabytes
  - E_KZ Gallery, circa circa 2002 -- 2017; UA244.002.00045; 5 Digital Object(s); 12.4 Megabytes
  - Freshman Retreat 2014, UA244.002.00046; 34 Digital Object(s); 150.4 Megabytes
  - From Digital Camera, circa circa 2008; UA244.002.00047; 141 Digital Object(s); 428.1 Megabytes
  - From the Center 2004 Pixs, UA244.002.00048; 32 Digital Object(s); 15.9 Megabytes
  - F_bbq, circa circa 2002 -- 2017; UA244.002.00049; 7 Digital Object(s); 20.8 Megabytes
  - Haiti 2013, UA244.002.00050; 65 Digital Object(s); 4.1 Megabytes
  - Haiti Alternative Spring Break 2013, UA244.002.00051; 5 Digital Object(s); 3.8 Megabytes
  - Hillel BBQ, circa circa 2002 -- 2017; UA244.002.00052; 18 Digital Object(s); 138.7 Megabytes
  - Hillel International Gala 2014, UA244.002.00053; 7 Digital Object(s); 13.2 Megabytes
  - Hillel Semiformal 2014, UA244.002.00054; 98 Digital Object(s); 60.5 Megabytes
  - Hillel Semiformal 2015, UA244.002.00055; 21 Digital Object(s); 142.3 Megabytes
  - H_ErinB, circa circa 2008 -- 2012; UA244.002.00056; 6 Digital Object(s); 33.6 Megabytes
  - India 2014, UA244.002.00057; 295 Digital Object(s); 710.8 Megabytes
  - Iniative for Innovative Community Building, circa circa 2002 -- 2017; UA244.002.00058; 6 Digital Object(s); 14.5 Megabytes
  - Interfaith Gingerbread House Making, circa circa 2002 -- 2017; UA244.002.00059; 24 Digital Object(s); 96.3 Megabytes
  - Isabel, circa circa 2002 -- 2017; UA244.002.00060; 19 Digital Object(s); 11.7 Megabytes
  - israel, circa circa 2002 -- 2017; UA244.002.00061; 63 Digital Object(s); 45.2 Megabytes
  - I_ReadRiver, circa circa 2002 -- 2017; UA244.002.00062; 5 Digital Object(s); 32.2 Megabytes
  - Jewish Farm School Alternative Spring Break 2014, UA244.002.00063; 89 Digital Object(s); 311 Megabytes
  - JWTS Zumba Class, circa circa 2002 -- 2017; UA244.002.00064; 7 Digital Object(s); 114.6 Megabytes
  - J_Sr. Shabbat, circa circa 2002 -- 2017; UA244.002.00065; 3 Digital Object(s); 8.9 Megabytes
  - Kazakhstan, circa circa 2002 -- 2017; UA244.002.00066; 38 Digital Object(s); 88.1 Megabytes
  - K_SemiFormal, circa circa 2002 -- 2017; UA244.002.00067; 6 Digital Object(s); 16.7 Megabytes
  - leading up north, circa circa 2002 -- 2017; UA244.002.00068; 8 Digital Object(s); 0.41 Megabytes
  - Lens Toward Peace 2005, UA244.002.00069; 12 Digital Object(s); 3.9 Megabytes
  - Let My People Go Remembering Soviet Jewry, circa circa 2002 -- 2017; UA244.002.00070; 14 Digital Object(s); 128.2 Megabytes
  - Local Food Fair, circa circa 2002 -- 2017; UA244.002.00071; 11 Digital Object(s); 22.8 Megabytes
  - Marcelo Brodsky Lecture, circa circa 2002 -- 2017; UA244.002.00072; 64 Digital Object(s); 375.7 Megabytes
  - Matriculation Day Open House 2013, UA244.002.00073; 11 Digital Object(s); 9.3 Megabytes
  - Matriculation Open House 2014, UA244.002.00074; 15 Digital Object(s); 27.3 Megabytes
  - Matriculation Open House 2015, UA244.002.00075; 13 Digital Object(s); 21.1 Megabytes
  - Miracle Martini 2009, UA244.002.00076; 45 Digital Object(s); 184.6 Megabytes
  - Moral Voices Keynote 2016, UA244.002.00077; 143 Digital Object(s); 793.4 Megabytes
  - Moshe Waldoks Lecture 2014, UA244.002.00078; 17 Digital Object(s); 63.5 Megabytes
  - New Board Old Board 2014, UA244.002.00079; 49 Digital Object(s); 170.8 Megabytes
  - Nicaragua, circa circa 2002 -- 2017; UA244.002.00080; 4 Digital Object(s); 6.8 Megabytes
  - October&November 2008, UA244.002.00081; 47 Digital Object(s); 242.8 Megabytes
  - Parents Weekend 2009, UA244.002.00082; 14 Digital Object(s); 65 Megabytes
  - Photos for Julie, circa circa 2002 -- 2017; UA244.002.00083; 3 Digital Object(s); 0.94 Megabytes
  - Pictures1, circa circa 2001 -- 2004; UA244.002.00084; 450 Digital Object(s); 534.5 Megabytes
  - Post Passover Palooza 2014, UA244.002.00085; 11 Digital Object(s); 41.8 Megabytes
  - Preparing for Rosh Hashanah, circa circa 2002 -- 2017; UA244.002.00086; 5 Digital Object(s); 11.5 Megabytes
  - Purim 2009, UA244.002.00087; 31 Digital Object(s); 52.8 Megabytes
  - Purim 2015, UA244.002.00088; 45 Digital Object(s); 71.1 Megabytes
  - Rabbi Jeffrey Summits 25th Anniversary, circa circa 2004; UA244.002.00089; 304 Digital Object(s); 460.4 Megabytes
  - RBTR 2009 Photos--Hanan Atia, UA244.002.00090; 29 Digital Object(s); 250.5 Megabytes
  - Read by the River, circa circa 2002 -- 2017; UA244.002.00091; 10 Digital Object(s); 57.8 Megabytes
  - Read by the River 2014, UA244.002.00092; 74 Digital Object(s); 281.8 Megabytes
  - Read by the River 2015, UA244.002.00093; 38 Digital Object(s); 357.4 Megabytes
  - Religious Pluralism in a Time of Extremism, circa circa 2002 -- 2017; UA244.002.00094; 57 Digital Object(s); 13.9 Megabytes
  - Rosh Hashannah & Lesley Portrait, circa circa 2002 -- 2017; UA244.002.00095; 37 Digital Object(s); 90 Megabytes
  - SemiFormal 2009, UA244.002.00096; 50 Digital Object(s); 122.2 Megabytes
  - Senior Shabbat, circa circa 2009; UA244.002.00097; 20 Digital Object(s); 65.6 Megabytes
  - Senior Shabbat 2014, UA244.002.00098; 8 Digital Object(s); 35.8 Megabytes
  - Sporkful Video, circa circa 2002 -- 2017; UA244.002.00099; 11 Digital Object(s); 28.9 Gigabytes
  - Survivors Speak 2014, UA244.002.00100; 35 Digital Object(s); 145.3 Megabytes
  - Survivors Speak Panel 2015, UA244.002.00101; 34 Digital Object(s); 355 Megabytes
  - Sustainable Harvest International - Honduras June 08, 2008; UA244.002.00102; 10 Digital Object(s); 8.6 Megabytes
  - Yom Hashoah Banners, circa circa 2002 -- 2017; UA244.002.00103; 7 Digital Object(s); 15.9 Megabytes
  - Young Alumni Meet and Greet 9.10.09, 2009; UA244.002.00104; 25 Digital Object(s); 1.2 Megabytes
  - 04-19-17 Dr. Munzer, 2017; UA244.002.00105; 1 Digital Object(s); 1.2 Gigabytes
  - Community Building Video_Final, circa circa 2002 -- 2017; UA244.002.00106; 1 Digital Object(s); 1.3 Gigabytes
  - Granoff_020911, 2011; UA244.002.00107; 1 Digital Object(s); 1.3 Gigabytes
  - hillel_ayalon10192010, UA244.002.00108; 1 Digital Object(s); 1.9 Gigabytes
  - hillel_Genocide_022411, 2011; UA244.002.00109; 1 Digital Object(s); 1.8 Gigabytes
  - tuftshillel_adam-and-eve-were-vegan_72157632742891747, circa circa 2002 -- 2017; UA244.002.00110; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.3 Megabytes
  - tuftshillel_alumni-cooking-with-tufts-first-lady-adele-bacow-april-3-2011_72157626633870495, UA244.002.00111; 1 Digital Object(s); 19.2 Megabytes
  - tuftshillel_alumni-night-2012_72157632632170189, UA244.002.00112; 1 Digital Object(s); 15.2 Megabytes
  - tuftshillel_amahoro-envision-the-future-of-rwanda_72157625413142665, circa circa 2002 -- 2017; UA244.002.00113; 1 Digital Object(s); 57.2 Megabytes
  - tuftshillel_argentina-service-trip-dinner_72157628080440980, circa circa 2002 -- 2017; UA244.002.00114; 1 Digital Object(s); 11.4 Megabytes
  - tuftshillel_bagel-brunch-2010_72157624915013311, UA244.002.00115; 1 Digital Object(s); 20.5 Megabytes
  - tuftshillel_birthright-pre-trip-orientation_72157631990425841, circa circa 2002 -- 2017; UA244.002.00116; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.2 Megabytes
  - tuftshillel_campus-center-mural_72157632747825840, circa circa 2002 -- 2017; UA244.002.00117; 1 Digital Object(s); 14.7 Megabytes
  - tuftshillel_chanukkah-casino-night---dec-2-2010_72157625418825689, UA244.002.00118; 1 Digital Object(s); 42.5 Megabytes
  - tuftshillel_chometz-fest_72157626552918716, circa circa 2002 -- 2017; UA244.002.00119; 1 Digital Object(s); 106.7 Megabytes
  - tuftshillel_cummings-lecture-john-pedergrast_72157633310991157, circa circa 2002 -- 2017; UA244.002.00120; 1 Digital Object(s); 136.9 Megabytes
  - tuftshillel_eve-ensler-at-the-merrin-moral-voices-distinguished-lecture-series_72157640970630355, circa circa 2002 -- 2017; UA244.002.00121; 1 Digital Object(s); 367 Megabytes
  - tuftshillel_farewell-celebration-for-judi-canter_72157631855036277, circa circa 2002 -- 2017; UA244.002.00122; 1 Digital Object(s); 14.6 Megabytes
  - tuftshillel_foi-event-steven-grossman_72157632870925148, circa circa 2002 -- 2017; UA244.002.00123; 1 Digital Object(s); 33.6 Megabytes
  - tuftshillel_freshmen-shabbat_72157627640593082, circa circa 2002 -- 2017; UA244.002.00124; 1 Digital Object(s); 4 Megabytes
  - tuftshillel_gay--religious--_72157627955162505, circa circa 2002 -- 2017; UA244.002.00125; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.3 Megabytes
  - tuftshillel_graduation-shabbat-5-20-2011_72157626679826665, UA244.002.00126; 1 Digital Object(s); 45.9 Megabytes
  - tuftshillel_hannukahfest_72157628472092033, circa circa 2002 -- 2017; UA244.002.00127; 1 Digital Object(s); 13.9 Megabytes
  - tuftshillel_hanukah_72157632228902698, circa circa 2002 -- 2017; UA244.002.00128; 1 Digital Object(s); 104.3 Megabytes
  - tuftshillel_hillel-alumni-happy-hour_72157627612348539, circa circa 2002 -- 2017; UA244.002.00129; 1 Digital Object(s); 67 Megabytes
  - tuftshillel_hillel-bagel-brunch_72157627516379607, circa circa 2002 -- 2017; UA244.002.00130; 1 Digital Object(s); 177.5 Megabytes
  - tuftshillel_hillel-board-meeting_72157625250597765, circa circa 2002 -- 2017; UA244.002.00131; 1 Digital Object(s); 61.6 Megabytes
  - tuftshillel_hillel-building_72157628471868321, circa circa 2002 -- 2017; UA244.002.00132; 1 Digital Object(s); 3.1 Megabytes
  - tuftshillel_hillel-elections_72157626907949286, circa circa 2002 -- 2017; UA244.002.00133; 1 Digital Object(s); 14.2 Megabytes
  - tuftshillel_hillel-open-house-2012_72157631311025636, UA244.002.00134; 1 Digital Object(s); 11.2 Megabytes